fon.com 2011-10-16

# Fon Privacy & Data Protection Policy

Fon Privacy & Data Protection Policy
We are Fon, a Community of people who share WiFi. As such, it is essential
that our users feel safe and secure both in the comfort of their homes/offices
and throughout our Community. This Privacy and Data Policy (hereinafter,
“Policy”) is a beta version. We hope that you will help us continuously improve
on this version to ensure that our Policy meets all of our Communityʼs needs
and expectations.
Furthermore, we hope that this Policy is flexible, clear, and easy to understand.
We have tried to use plain language wherever possible.
Fon Wireless Ltd (hereinafter, “Fon”), fully complies with the current legislation
regarding the protection of data of a personal nature, and with the confidentiality
commitments characteristic of the activity that it undertakes. Furthermore, Fon
complies with the UK Protection Act 1998, complementary regulation and other
relevant legislation.
All of your personal data that Fon receives and stores shall be kept in a file
called “Clients File”. We have notified the Data Protection Commissioner of this
with the registration number Z9433580. Fon Wireless Limited, a UK company,
domiciled at 8 Clifford Street, W1S 2LQ and registered at the Company House
of London under the No 5661131 is solely responsible for this file. The data filed
is adequate, appropriate and does not exceed the scope, purpose, and goals of
the services that Fon provides.
The purpose of this file is for Fon to better serve its users as well as to maintain
contact with them. Fon may also use the data to send commercial information
as well as for any other purpose Fon deems to be in the interest of its users.
The treatment of personal data and its use for commercial communications
purposes complies with the applicable legislation.
Fon has adopted the technical measures necessary to maintain the security
level required, according to the nature of the personal data processed and the
circumstances of this processing, with the objective of avoiding (in the realm of
the possible and always using the latest in technology) its alteration, loss,
processing or non-authorized access.
You know and accept that the access and information about the access through
each Hotspot is governed by the laws of the country where it is located. You
know and accept that joining the Fon Community gives you access to Hotspots
around the globe. Access points in different countries may be subject to differing
local laws, and we may be required to store data to comply with those laws. The
Privacy and Data Protection Policies and the Terms & Conditions applicable to
the Hotspot through which you are connecting will always be available through
the registration process or at www.Fon.com.
Fon Privacy Policy 2011                                                            1

Please recognize that this Policy only applies to how Fon deals with your
privacy and your personal information. It does not apply to any other company
or to any other company's websites even if you access them through Fonʼs
Community or once you have left the Fon Community. If you disclose your
personal information to other companies your information will be dealt with
according to their privacy practices.
Fon Respects your Privacy
You accept and agree that Fon needs to share the address of your access point
to enable other Foneros to find it. You will contact us through our customer care
support service if you want to edit the location information to make it less
specific – for example, removing the apartment or suite number from an
address, or giving a street number range (8 – 14 Main Street) rather than a
precise number, and fuzz the geolocation data. These fuzzed addresses will be
visible in forms such as Fon maps and directories of nearby access points. We
will not publicly associate your name with your address and access point, and
we will not make your name or more specific address available to third parties.
We may allow third parties to access the list of fuzzed addresses for such
purposes as creating hotspot maps. We cannot guarantee that third parties will
not be able to deduce your precise address.
We will not sell or share your personal data to third parties without your consent.
You agree and accept that the data you provide to Fon can be shared between
companies of Fon´s Group within the scope of this Policy.
In the future, Fon may offer additional services. For those additional services,
other privacy policies may apply. If this be the case, we will ask you to review
them carefully.
You are permitted to exercise your rights to access, amend, delete and contest
the data you have provided. Should you wish to notify us in this respect, send
us your written request to Fon WIRELESS Limited, by email to:
privacy@Fon.com. Do not forget to clearly state the right you wish to exercise.
This policy is subject to change based upon modification to the current
applicable law. If the policy changes, you will be notified on your next login and
will have the opportunity to cancel our service if you are not satisfied with these
changes.
Fonʼs goal is to respect your privacy to the best of its ability. Please contact us
at privacy@Fon.com with suggestions for improving this Policy.
Fon Privacy Policy 2011                                                           2
